UNITE Department of Occupational Safety and Health Shop Files 6000/019
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Department of Occupational Safety and Health Shop Files
1995- 2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
UNITE Department of Occupational Safety and Health
6000/019
16.5 cubic feet
16.5 linear ft.
Records.
6791847
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 17, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619/015: ACTWU Department of Occupational Safety and Health Files 6000 AV: UNITE Audio-Visual Collection 6000 G: UNITE Posters 6000 MB: UNITE Memorabilia 6000 P: UNITE Photographs
Laundry workers--Labor unions; Textile workers--Labor unions; Clothing workers--Labor unions; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives; Laundry, Dry Cleaning, and Dye House Workers International Union --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees. Department of Occupational Safety and Health--Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives
6791847
- D. Glasgow & Sons (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Malden Mills - 1995 Fire (Box 1, Folder 2)
- North American Plastics Corp. Chicago, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Scope and Contents
  March
- Shumsky Closure Inc., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Hazard by Industry New Tech. - Modular MFG (Box 1, Folder 5)
- OSHA Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Byssinosis US Government - Cotton Dust STD 1998 Reg Flex - Act Review (Box 1, Folder 7)
- OSH Case - Amalgamated Service & Allied Industries Joint BD. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- OSH Case American Down Textile Co. La Crosse, WI (Box 1, Folder 9)
- OSH Case American Spirit Mailing (Box 1, Folder 10)
- OSH Case Ameripride Linen & Apparel (Box 1, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Ameripride Linen & Apparel Services - Route Sales (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Hartford, CT
- OSH Case Ameripride Uniform (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Fresno, CA
- OSH Case Ameriwood Ind. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Wright City, MO
- OSH Case Amertex Service Group (Box 1, Folder 15)
- OSH Case Ametek (Box 1, Folder 16)
- OSH Case Anibal Travieso (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Bronx, NY
- OSH Case Aramak General (Box 1, Folder 18)
- OSH Case Aramak Corp. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Toledo, OH
- OSH Case Aramak Uniform Services Inc. Bowling Green, MC (Box 1, Folder 20)
- OSH Case Aramak Uniform Services, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 21)
- OSH Case Aramak Uniform Services, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Bakersfield, Fresno, Modesto, CA
- OSH Case Aramak Uniform Services, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Reading, PA
- OSH Aramak Uniform Services, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Portland, OR
- OSH Case Atlantic City Linen Supply, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 25)
- OSH Case Atlas Health Care Linen Services (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Atrium Case File (Box 1, Folder 27)
- OSH Case Bemis Co. (Box 1, Folder 28)
- OSH Case Best Form Foundations, Inc. - Johnstown, PA (Box 1, Folder 29)
- OSH Case Beverly Enterprises - Ergo OSHA Settlement (Box 1, Folder 30)
- OSH Case Breed, Inc. (Form Allied Signal) (Box 1, Folder 31)
  Knoxville, TN
- OSH Case Breed Technologies Co. (Box 1, Folder 32)
- OSH Case Brooks Bros. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  Kinston, NC
- OSH Case Celanese Corp. (Box 1, Folder 34)
  Narrows, VA
- OSH Corn Century Circuits (Box 1, Folder 35)
  St. Paul, MN
- OSH Case Champion Dyeing & Finishing Co. (Box 1, Folder 36)
  Paterson, NJ
- OSH Case Century Circuits (Box 1, Folder 36)
  St. Pauls, MN
- OSH Case Churchill Linen Service, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 37)
- OSH Case Cintas Corp. (Box 1, Folder 38)
  Detroit, MI
- OSH Case Clean Rental Services (Box 1, Folder 39)
- OSH Case Cloquet Community Memorial Hospital (Box 1, Folder 40)
- OSH Case Crescent Sleeping Prod. (Box 1, Folder 41)
  Greensboro, NC
- OSH Case Crystal Art (Box 1, Folder 42)
  Maspeth, NY
- OSH Case Crystal Art (Box 1, Folder 43)
- OSH Case Crystal Art (Box 2, Folder 1)
- OSH Case Dcor LTD. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Domestic Linen Supply Co. (Box 2, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Domestic Uniform (Box 2, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Drieson Int'l (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Cleveland, OH
- OSH Case Drieson Int'l OSHA Inspection Cleveland, OH (Box 2, Folder 6)
- OSH Case Dreison Int'l - Collective Bargaining (Box 2, Folder 7)
- OSH Case Dreison Int'l (Box 2, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Economy Linen Serv. Inc. (Box 2, Folder 9)
- OSH Case The Ensign-Brickford (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Simsbury, CT
- OSH Case FDR Services Inc.(American Eagle Commercial Laundry Corp.) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Freeport, NY
- OSH Case Fiberdye, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 12)
- OSH Case Fieldcrest Cannon (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Spencer, NC
- OSH Case Fieldcrest Cannon (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Eden, NC
- OSH Case Fieldcrest Cannon (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Kannapolis, NC
- OSH Case Fieldcrest Cannon Election 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- OSH Case Fieldcrest Cannon (Box 2, Folder 17)
- OSH Case Findlay Ind. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Chesterfield, MO
- OSH Case Findlay Industries Inc. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Springfield, OH
- OSH Case Fingerhut Co. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Mora, MN
- OSH Case Flambeau Corp. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Roanoke Rapids, NC
- OSH Case Freudenberg (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Bristol, NV
- OSH Case G & K Services Industrial Div. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Minneapolis, MN
- OSH Case G&K Services Industrial Div. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  New Orleans, LA
- OSH Case G&K Services Ind. Div. (Box 2, Folder 25)
- GAF Corp. (Box 2, Folder 26)
- OSH Case Goya Foods (Box 2, Folder 27)
  Miami, FL
- Goya Foods (Box 2, Folder 28)
- OSH Case Guilford Mills (Penn Dye) (Box 2, Folder 29)
  Pine Grove, PA
- OSH Case H&P Ind. General (Box 2, Folder 30)
  Mukwonago, WI
- OSH Case Harrisburg MFG Co. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  Harrisburg, IL
- OSH Case Hartmarx (Hickey Freeman Div.) (Box 2, Folder 32)
  Rochester, NY
- OSH Case Napp Tech (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Conventry, RI
- OSH Case Napp OSHA/EPA Report (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Lodi, NJ
- OSH Case Napp OSHA/EPA Report - Peer Review (Box 3, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Napp Tech - Citations (Box 3, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Napp Tech General (Box 3, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Napp Tech Clippings (Box 3, Folder 6)
- OSH Case National Linen (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Case National Linen - Collective Bargaining, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- OSH Case National Linen - Negotiations, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- OSH Case National Linen - Health & Safety Contract, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  August
- OSH Case Nautica Int'l Inc. (Box 3, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Nylonge Corp. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Elyria, OH
- OSH Case Ocean Side Institutional Ind. (Box 3, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Owens-Corning Collective Bargaining, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Guelph, Ontario
- OSH Case Owens-Corning Ergonomics (Box 3, Folder 15)
- OSH Case Owens-Corning Ergonomics (Box 4, Folder 1)
- OSH Case Owens corning - Environmental Industrial Hygiene (Box 4, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Owens-Corning - Man Made Fibers (Box 4, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Owens-corning - Negotiations (Box 4, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Owens-Corning (Box 4, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Pactive, Inc. Malverne, WI (Box 4, Folder 6)
- OSH Case Parabal Corp. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Las Vegas, NV
- OSH Case Pearl Paint Corp. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Peerless Umbrella Co. Inc. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Harrison, NJ
- OSH Case Petit Jean Poultry (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Arkadelphia, AR
- OSH Case Petit Jean Poultry (Box 4, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Phillips - Moldex Co. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Putnam, CT
- OSH Case Phoenix Medical (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Andrews, SC
- OSH Case Pine Shirt Company (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Pottsville, PA
- OSH Case Plastonics, Inc (Box 4, Folder 15)
- OSH Case Pliant Corp. (Formerly Goodyear Corp.) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  Calhoun, GA
- OSH Case Rapid Industrial Plastics (Box 4, Folder 17)
  Jersey City, NJ
- OSH Case Resistol Hat Co. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  Garland, TX
- OSH Case Riva Jewelry MFG Inc. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  Long Island City, NY
- RJ McCarthy Ltd. (Box 4, Folder 20)
- OSH Case Robison & Smith, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  Gloversville, NY
- OSH Case Rocky Shoes & Boots (Box 4, Folder 22)
- OSH Case Royal Laundry (Box 4, Folder 23)
  Somerville, MA
- OSH Case S & K Plastics Inc. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Brooklyn, NY
- OSH Case Safelight Glass Corp. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Enfield, NC
- OSH Case Sealy Mattress Co. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Sequins Int'l (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Queens, NY
- OSH Case Specialty Filaments, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Burlington, VT
- OSH Case Steiner Corp. American Linen (Box 5, Folder 6)
  San Francisco, CA
- OSH Case Steiner Corp. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Boise, ID
- OSH Case Tahari LTD. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  New York, NY
- OSH Tartan Textile Serv. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Portland, ME
- OSH Case Tartan Textile (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Clermont, FL
- OSH Case Tartan Textile (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Patterson, NJ
- OSH Case Tenneco Corp. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Malverne, AR
- OSH Case Texas Apparel (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Carrizo Spring, TX
- OSH Case T.J. Maxx (Box 5, Folder 14)
- OSH Case TR MFG Inc. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  Lancaster, NY
- OSH Case Triple A in the USA (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Belfair, OH
- Tultex Co. (Box 5, Folder 17)
- OSH Case Tyson Foods, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 18)
- OSH Case United Parcel Service (Box 5, Folder 19)
- OSH Case United Veil, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 20)
- OSH Case Unitex (Box 5, Folder 21)
- OSH Case Up to Date Laundry, Inc. Bargaining Agreement w/ UNITE (Box 5, Folder 22)
- OSH Case Van Dyke Crotty, Inc. Bargaining Agreement w/ UNITE (Box 5, Folder 23)
- OSH Case VF Playwear (Box 5, Folder 24)
  Danville, VA
- OSH Case Wellman Inc. Fibers Div. (Box 5, Folder 25)
  Johnsonville, SC
- OSH Case Wilson Sporting Goods (Box 5, Folder 26)
  Ada, OH
- OSH Case Woodlawn, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 27)
  Aliquippa, PA
- OSH Case Woodbridge Group (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Wellman Industries (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Windsor Textiles (Box 5, Folder 30)
- OSH Case Woonsockett Spinning Co. (Box 5, Folder 31)
  Charlotte, NC
- OSH Case Workpros Inc. (Box 5, Folder 32)
- OSH Case Xerox Corp. (Box 5, Folder 33)
  Webster, NY
- OSH Case Zeta Plastics - Tucker Div. (Box 5, Folder 34)
  Arlington, TX
- OSHA - Eric Frumin (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Census of Fatal Occupational Injuries, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- UNITE! Health and Safety (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Yale University Strike, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Cintas (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Laundry (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Income Statements (Box 6, Folder 7)
- US Department of Labor - Citation and Notification of Penalty (Box 6, Folder 8)
- skin Problems, etc. (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Monorails and Underhung Cranes (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Occupational Health Watch (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Misc. (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Breaking Ranks with the AFL-CIO (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Breaking Ranks with the AFL-CIO (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Safety Action Plan (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Establishment Search Inspection Detail (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Endocrine-Disrupting Chemicals (Box 6, Folder 17)
- UNITE! (Box 6, Folder 18)
- DLTP Curriculum (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Occupational Safety & Health (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Paid Time off reports - Ergonomic Seating (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Laundry, Stealing It (Box 6, Folder 22)
- OSHA, AFL-CIO (Box 6, Folder 23)
- TTX - MSDS (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Fauvecia (Box 6, Folder 25)
- UNITE! Laundry (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Jaresville (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Daily Press Clips - Strategic Affairs (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Eric Frumin UNITE! (Box 6, Folder 29)
- AFL-CIO (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Carl Zichella - Sierra Club (Box 6, Folder 31)
- AFL-CIO (Box 6, Folder 32)
- UNITE! Negotiations Timeline (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Material Safety Data Sheet (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Ergonomics (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Chemical Exposure (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Medical Reports (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Misc. (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Misc. (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Misc. (Box 6, Folder 40)
- OSH Case Health-Tex Inc. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Centreville, AL
- OSH Case Hebrew Home for the Aged (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Highland Light Steam Laundry Inc. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Peekskill, NY
- OSH Case Hospital Central Services Cooperative Inc. (HCSC) (Box 7, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Highland Yarn Mills (Box 7, Folder 5)
- OSH Case ICM Corp. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Cicero, NY
- OSH Case Industrial Plastics (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Strongville, OH
- OSH Case Janesville Products (Box 7, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Janesville Products (Box 7, Folder 9)
- OSH Case Janesville Products (Box 7, Folder 10)
- OSH Case K-Mart Corp. (Box 7, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Janesville Products (Box 7, Folder 12)
- OSH Case Kleen Brite Lab Inc. (Box 8, Folder 1)
- OSH Case Lear Corp. - General (Box 8, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Lear Corp., Inc. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Midland, TX
- OSH Case Lear Corp. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Freemont, OH
- OSH Case Lear Corp. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Carlisle, PA
- OSH Case Leslie Fay (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Laflin, PA
- OSH Case Leslie Fay Co., Inc. (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Ergonomic Work Group Letters From E.F. (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Letters to Levis Staff & Council (Including Notes) (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Levis Ergo Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 10)
- OSH Case - Levi Strauss - Collective Bargaining - Dry Testing (Box 8, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Levi Strauss (Box 8, Folder 12)
  Hebron, KY
- OSH Case Levi Strauss (Box 8, Folder 13)
  Henderson, NV
- OSH Case Levi Strauss Levi Council (Box 8, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Levis Strauss Workloads (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Levi's Training (Box 8, Folder 16)
- OSH Case Lion Apparel (Box 8, Folder 17)
- OSH Case Lion Apparel (Box 8, Folder 18)
  Williamsburg, KY
- OSH Case Liz Claiborne, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 19)
- OSH Case Liz Claiborne (Box 8, Folder 20)
  Montgomery, AL
- Case Lumex, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  Johnstown, NY
- OSH Case Maidenform, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 22)
  Jacksonville, FL
- OSH Casae Malden Mills 1995 Fire (Box 8, Folder 23)
- OSH Case Manhattan Beer - General (Box 8, Folder 24)
  Wyandanch, NY
- OSH Case Maramont corp. (Box 8, Folder 25)
- OSH Case Marijon Co. (Box 8, Folder 26)
  E. Rutherford, NJ
- OSH Case Martin Linen Co. (Box 8, Folder 27)
  San Antonio, TX
- OSH Case Mayfield Cap Co. (Box 8, Folder 28)
  Mayfield, KY
- OSH Case McWane Corp. (Box 8, Folder 29)
- OSH Case Midwest Textile Service Association (MTSA) (Box 8, Folder 30)
- OSH Case Mission Linen Supply (Box 8, Folder 31)
- OSH Case Mission Linen Supply (Box 8, Folder 32)
- OSH Case Mssion of NV, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 33)
- OSH Case Mitchellace, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 34)
  Portsmouth, OH
- OSH Case Monroe Print/Franco MFG. (Box 8, Folder 35)
  Monroe, NC
- OSH Case Monterey Mills (Box 8, Folder 36)
  Janesvolle, WI
- Legislation (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Grass Roots Targets (Box 9, Folder 2)
- UNITE! (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Eric Frumin (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Paper Towel (Box 9, Folder 5)
- OSHA/OHS (Box 9, Folder 6)
- US Government Organizations (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Misc. (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Cintas (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Interoffice Mail (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Financial (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Cintas (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Grants (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Misc. (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Misc. (Box 9, Folder 15)
- UNITE! (Box 9, Folder 16)
- AFL (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Misc. (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Misc., UNITE! (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Fingerhut Companies OSHA 200 Log (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Eric Frumin (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Ergonomics (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Ergo Std (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Misc. (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Ergonomics Programs UAW Joint Company Program (Box 10, Folder 6)
- NYCOSH (Box 10, Folder 7)
- OSHA Ergo (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Cases from Shops (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Barneys NY (ELBALIZ) (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Perfect Shoulder (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Tartan Hempstead (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Tartan - Freeport (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Best Metropolitan (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Polo Linen Long I (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Princeton (Box 10, Folder 16)
- White Plains Inp. (Box 10, Folder 17)
- White Plains Linen (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Seacrest - Laundry (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Laundry Material (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Unitex Negotiations (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Laundry - ASAIJB - Union Representation - To OSHA (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Oceanside (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Safety Signs Laundry (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Unitex - Bronx (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Unitex - Hartford, CT (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Unitex - Mt. Vernon (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Navigation - Chinese (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Grant Letters and Proposals (Box 10, Folder 30)
- PDF Directory (Box 10, Folder 31)
- UNITE (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Grant Support Materials, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Committees - Inspect Accident Investigation (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Lesson Plans - H and S Committees Excercises and Role Plays (Box 11, Folder 4)
- H and S Committees - Training and Info (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Extra H and S Committee Materials (Box 11, Folder 6)
- H and S Committees: Group Activity Questions Problems (Box 11, Folder 7)
- H & S Committee (Box 11, Folder 8)
- OSHA Inspection - Span. (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Spanish (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Levantamiento Lifting and Backs (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Asbestos (Box 11, Folder 12)
- SIDA/HIV (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Tubercliosis - Spanish (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Warehouse Safety (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Manhattan Beer (Box 11, Folder 16)
- OSHA - Inform. (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Sample Letters OSHA Walk Around Multiple copies (Box 11, Folder 18)
- OSHA Standards (Box 11, Folder 19)
- OSH (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Machine Guarding Info./Lockout Exercises (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Spanish - Machine Guarding (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Fire Safety Fact Sheets (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Fire Safety Training Materials (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Stress / Training Material (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Noise (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Prevencion de Acidentes: Mitos y Realidades (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Reproductive Haz (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Job Stress - Good Materials (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Role Plays - Wrist Dialog Workers Comp. (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Warehouse: Group Exercises (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Stress Lesson Plans (education) (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Hazard Tree (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Game and Icebreakers (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Hazard Tree (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Organizing Health and Safety (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Games and Icebreakers (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Programs/Incentives Behavior Prog. (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Factsheets Poster Training (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Committee (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Mechanic Class, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  September 6
- Basic New Train The Trainer Program -, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  September 25-26, October 2-3
- Leadership Training (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Basci Train The Trainer Program, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  Oct.
- Training for Advanced Programs (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Curriculum Development Training (Box 12, Folder 8)
- UNITE! (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Noise Lesson Plan (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Ergonomics (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Training Exercises (Box 12, Folder 12)
- UNITE! (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Organizing Campaign - WETSCH. (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 15)
- OSHA Law and Regs, General (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Protection for Discrimination (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Legal Rights of Workers - General - H & S (Box 12, Folder 18)
- OSHA Sample Logs and Complaint (Box 12, Folder 19)
- EMZAR Local 62-32 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Feldman Local 62-32 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Riva Jewelry Manufacturing (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Pearl Paint (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Letters (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Inspections, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Protective Equipment - gloves/Laundry Health Care Workers (Box 12, Folder 26)
- PERC and Ventilation Clean System (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Inspection Material, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Laundry Bulletins (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Truck and Safety Laundries (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Contract Language and Negotiations (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Contract Rampage (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Ergonomics - Back Injuries (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Local 23-25 Contract Language (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Eric Frumin (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Health & Safety (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Ergonomics (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Correspondences, Info, Misc. (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Corres., Info, Misc. 2 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- UNITE! Health and Safety (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Crystal, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Crystal Art (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Pace (Box 14, Folder 3)
- OSHA Investing (Box 14, Folder 4)
- ACC, etc. (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Fax, Eric Frumin (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Press (Box 14, Folder 7)
- CSB (Box 14, Folder 8)
- NFPA (Box 14, Folder 9)
- ANPR (Box 14, Folder 10)
- CSB - Other (Box 14, Folder 11)
- CSB Docs (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Napp - WMD 1996, 1998, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- OSH - Emey - Hazwoper (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Center for Chemical Process Safety or the American Institute of Chemical Engineers Guidelines for Chemical Reactivity Evaluation and Application to Process Design (Box 14, Folder 15)
- OSHA Documents (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Lodi Explosion (Box 14, Folder 17)
- UNITE - chemical safety documents (Box 14, Folder 18)
- UNITE - Department of Occupational Safety & Health (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Center for Chemical Process Safety Essential Practices for Managing Chemical Reactivity Hazards (Box 14, Folder 20)
- US Chemical Safety and Hazard Investigation Board. Various Documents (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Lodi Explosion Hearing Document UNITE CSB Napp Technologies (Box 14, Folder 22)
- John Gray Institute Safety and Health Practices Study (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Information Kits (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Process Safety Management Regulations (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Lodi Explosion (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Lodi Explosion (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Lodi Explosion (Box 15, Folder 6)
- OSHA Files (Box 15, Folder 7)
- OSH Case - Gardner MFG (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Forklifts (Box 15, Folder 9)
- PA Project Training Materials (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Ergonomics Literature (Box 15, Folder 11)
- OSH Icem (Box 15, Folder 12)
- OSH ICFTU Toy Campaign (Box 15, Folder 13)
- ITGLWF (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Radiation (Box 15, Folder 15)
- OSH Statistics Massachusetts (MA) (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Bureau of Labor Statistics (Box 15, Folder 17)
- BLS LRAC (Box 15, Folder 18)
- OSH Admin Congressional Oversight, 1998-2002 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- OSH Admin Congressional Oversight, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Review Commission (Box 16, Folder 2)
- OSH Admin Labor Dept. Enforcement CCP-NJ (Box 16, Folder 3)
- OSH Admin Labor Dept Enforcement CCP (Box 16, Folder 4)
- OSH Admin Labor Dept Record Keeping Rule, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- OSH Admin Labor Dept Enforcement CCP NY (Box 16, Folder 6)
- OSH Admin Labor Dept Record Keeping Revision, 1995-2000 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- OSH Admin Labor Dept Record Keeping (Box 16, Folder 8)
- OSH Admin Recordkeeping Proposed Rule, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- OSH Admin Labor Dept Recordkeeping Proposed Revisions Procedural Issues (Box 16, Folder 10)
- OSH Admin Niosh Board of Scientific Counselors (B.S.C.) (Box 16, Folder 11)
- OSH Admin Niosh Board of Scientific Counselors Diesel Study (Box 16, Folder 12)
- NIOSH General, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Ergonomics Survey English (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Contract Language (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Crystal Art (Box 17, Folder 3)